Guide to the Laboratory for Elementary Particle Physics records, 1953-2010.
Laboratory for Elementary Particle Physics records
- Series III: Cornell Lab of Nuclear Studies Notes (CLNS)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1691-1703, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1704-1716, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1717-1726, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1727-1730, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1731-1741, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1742, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1743-1756, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1757-1766, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1767-1777, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1778-1784, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1785-1794, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1800-1812, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1813-1828, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Laboratory of Nuclear Studies (CLNS) Notes - #1829-1857, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Cleo Draft, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Cleo Draft, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Cleo Draft, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Cleo Draft, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Cleo Draft, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Cleo Draft, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Cleo Draft, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Cleo Draft, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Cleo Draft, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Cleo II Notes, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Cleo II Notes, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Cleo II Software, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Cleo II Software, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Cleo III Particle ID Status Meeting, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Series IV: CSN
  - CSN, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - CSN, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - CSN, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - CSN, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - CSN, 1985-1989 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - CSN, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - CSN, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - CSN, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - CSN, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - CSN, 1992-1995 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - CSN, 1995-1998 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Series V: Cornell Electron Storage Ring (CESR/CLEO) Proposals, Reports, Presentations
  - CON(CESR Operations Notes), 1984 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - CON, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - CON, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - CON, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - CON, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - CON, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - CON, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - CON, 1991-1994 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - CON, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - CON, 1997-2002 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Electron Storage Ring (CESR) Design Report, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - (CESR) Design Report, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Electron-Position Colliding Beam Facility, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for a High Energy X-Ray Synchrotron Radiation Laboratory, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Progress Report on Design and Development Study for CESR II, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Progress Report on Design Study for CESR II, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Appendices to Progress Report on Design Study for CESR II, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - CESR Impact Analysis, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - CESR Proposal for Addition to Wilson Synchrotron, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - CLEO II A Proposal for Upgrade of the Cleo Detector, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - CLEO II Updated Proposal for Improvements of the Cleo Detector, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Report to the CESR PAC, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - CESR Proposal to Construct an Addition to the Wilson Synchrotron, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Report to the CESR PAC, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Prospects for CESR B-Factory Upgrade, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Report to the CESR PAC, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - CESR B-Factory Upgrade, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Proposal for a B-Factory Upgrade for CESR, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - CESR Physics Rationale for a B-Factory, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - CESR Detector for a B-Factory, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Conceptual Design for a B-Factory Based on CESR, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Revised Proposal for a B-Factory Upgrade for the CESR, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - B-Factory/CLEO Collaboration (Leadership teams of Teachers and Scientists), 1991 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - CESR B-Factory, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - CLEO Presentations to the Physics Advisory Committee, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - CLEO Collaboration Report to the Physics Advisory Committee, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - CESR Presentations to the Physics Advisory Committee, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Report of the CESR Program Advisory Committee, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - CLEO Collaboration Report to the Physics Advisory Committee, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - CESR Physics Rationale for a B-Factory, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - CESR B-Factory Report, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - CESR Updated Proposal for B-Factory Upgrade, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Conceptual Design for a B-Factory Based on CESR, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - CESR Detector for a B-Factory, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Selection of the Preferred Stie for the B-Factory, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Funds for addition to Wilson Synchrotron, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - CESR History, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - CLEO III Detector Upgrade Project, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - CLEO III Detector Status Report, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - CLEO Collaboration Report to the Physics Advsiory Committee, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Physics Advisory Committee (PAC) Meeting CESR Performance: Presentations to the PAC, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Report of the CESR/CLEO Advisory Committee, January 1994 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Report of CESR Program Advisory Committee, November 1994 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Report of the CESR/CLEO Advisory Committee, November 1995 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - CLEO III Detector Status Report, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - CLEO III Detector Status Report, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Physics Advisory Committee Talks: CESR Status, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Report of the CESR/CLEO Advisory Committee, December 1996 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - CLEO Collaboration Papers, 1997-1998 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Report of the CESR/CLEO Advisory Committee, December 1997 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Report of the CESR/CLEO Advisory Committee, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - CESR Annual Progress Report, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Cleo III Status Reports, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Cleo III Status Reports, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Cost Estimate for CESR -B, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Cost Estimate for CESR - B, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Joint B Factory Review, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Joint B Factory Review, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Report of the Joint DOE and NSF B-Factory Review Committee, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Response to the B-Factory Review Charge, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Environmental Assessment for Proposed B-Factory, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - CESR Annual Progress Report, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - CESR Annual Progress Report, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - CESR Annual Progress Report, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - CESR Proposal for Support, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - CESR Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - CESR Quarterly Reports, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - CESR Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Operational Support, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Physics Goals for CESR II, no date (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Series VI: Energy Recovery Linac (ERL)
  - Energy Recovery Linac (ERL), 2001 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - ERL, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - ERL, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - ERL, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - ERL, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - ERL, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - ERL, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - ERL Reports, 2002-2006 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - ERL Meetings, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Series VII: National Science Foundation
  - Proposal to the National Science Foundation for a 3 BEV Synchrotron, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Proposal to the National Science Foundation for a 10 GEV Synchrotron, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Continuation of Design Studies for a 10 GEV Synchrotron, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Accelerator Improvement, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - NSF (National Science Foundation), 1967-1971 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - NSF, 1972-1977 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Proposal to the National Science Foundation for Construction Funds, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Appendices to the National Science Foundation for Proposal for Construction Funds, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - NSF, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - NSF, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - NSF, 1981-1983 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - NSF, 1984-1986 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - NSF, 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - NSF, 1989-1992 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - NSF, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - NSF, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - NSF, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - NSF, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - NSF, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - NSF, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - NSF, 1999-2001 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - NSF Special Emphasis Panel, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - NSF Agreement Quarterly Reports, 1973-1977 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - NSF Agreement Quarterly Reports, 1978-1980 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - NSF Agreement Quarterly Reports, 1981-1985 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - NSF Agreement Quarterly Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - NSF Agreement Quarterly Reports, 1989-1992 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - NSF Agreement Quarterly Reports, 1993-1997 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - NSF Agreement Quarterly Reports, 1998-2002 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Series VIII: Other Proposals, Reports, Manuals, Memos and Articles
  - Laboratory of Nuclear Studies Annual Reports, 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory of Nuclear Studies Annual Reports, 1971-1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Laboratory of Nuclear Studies Annual Reports, 1974-1980 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Laboratory of Nuclear Studies Annual Reports, 1980-1985 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Laboratory of Nuclear Studies Annual Reports, 1985-1991 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Laboratory of Nuclear Studies Progress Report, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Laboratory of Nuclear Studies Progress Report, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Articles, Memos, Correspondence, Programs concerning the synchrotron lab, 1950s-1960s (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Cornell 300-MEV Synchrotron Report, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Cornell BEV Synchrotron Report, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Electron Accelerator Project, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Proposal for a 10 GEV Electron Synchrotron, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Final Report: Office of Naval Research Contract Nonr 401-26, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Site Feasibility Study for Electron Synchrotron Laboratory, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - 10 GEV Electron Synchrotron at Cornell Report, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Specifications for Tunnel and Site Preparation, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - General Conditions for Tunnel and Site Preparation, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Memos, Budgets, Correspondence concerning the business of the 10 GEV Synchrotron Project, 1965-1966 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Appendix: Plans for Experiments on the 10 GEV Synchrotron, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Anecdotal Account of Accelerators at Cornell, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Report on the 10 to 20 GEV Synchrotron, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Newspapers Clippings about the Laboratory of Nuclear Studies, 1967-1987 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Articles, Memos, Correspondence, Programs concerning the Laboratory of Nuclear Studies, 1970-1982 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Report on the 10 GEV Synchrotron Program, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Proposal for funds to construct an addition to the 10 GEV Synchrotron Facility, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Cornell Electron Accelerator Program, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Cornell Electron Synchrotron Program, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Proposal for a Stie and Injection Scheme for a 50x50 GEV e+e-Colliding Beam Machine at Cornell- by J. Seeman, November 1979 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Articles and Programs from the Dedication of Cornell Electron Storage Ring, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Design Study High Luminosity Electron Collider, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Detectors and Experiments for 100 GEV, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Detectors and Experiments for 100 GEV, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - North Area Proposal from Columbia-Stony Brook, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Articles, Memos, Correspondence, Programs concerning the Laboratory of Nuclear Studies, 1983-1985 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Report of the 20 TeV Hadron Collider, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Upsilon Physics CUSB, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Upsilon Physics CUSB II, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Schematic Design Report - Addition to Wilson Laboratory, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Upsilon Physics CUSB II, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Upsilon Physics CUSB II, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Upsilon Physics CUSB II, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - Appendix: Proposed Long Term Program TEV Collider, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - Cornell's Program in Super Conducting RF, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Statement of Work Cavity Procurement, September 1988 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Electron Storage Ring Report, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - International Linear Collider Technical Review Committee Report, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - MUON Storage Ring Proposal, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Articles, Correspondence concerning Robert Wilson's Death, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Cleanroom Proposal for Newman Laboratory, April 2001 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - LCCOM (Linear Collider Consortium Organizational Meeting), 2002 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - LCCOM (Linear Collider Consortium Organizational Meeting), 2002 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Physics Advisory Committee, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Physics Advisory Committee, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Factories, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Factories, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Factories, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Operating Manual-AM/FM Signal Generator 2023A, 2023B, 2025, June 2005 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Diagrams of Circuits, Control Room, etc., no date (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Maintenance Manual of the CESR RF System, no date (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Zeiss Calypso, 2006-2007 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - RF Superconductivity, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - HEPAP (High Energy Physics Advisory Panel), 1983, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - HEPAP Sub Panel, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - HEPAP, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - HEPAP, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - HEPAP, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - HEPAP, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Log books, 1984, 1995, 2000-2002 (Box 31)
  - Report - Two Problems in the Kenetic Theory of Plasmas, 1964 (Box 31)
  - Report - Ionospheric Heating by Magnetic Conjugate Point Photoelectrons, 1965 (Box 31)
  - Report - Radative Transfer in a Gas Excited by X-RAYS, 1967 (Box 31)
  - Report - Models of Compact X-RAY Sources, 1973 (Box 31)
- Series IX: Conferences, Workshops
  - CHESS Conference- Introductory Remarks by P. Hartman, July 1981 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Program for Symposium Honoring Boyce McDaniel, May 1985 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Syracuse University Workshop on a B-Factory, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Workshop on Measuring B-Meson Decay with Upgraded CLEO Detector, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - SRF Mini Workshop, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - SRF Meeting Minutes, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - SRF Meeting Minutes, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - APS Cleo Talks, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - APS Cleo Talks, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - APS Cleo Talks, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - CBX Cleo Conference, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - CBX Cleo Conference, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - CBX Cleo Conference, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - CBX Cleo Conference, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - CBX Cleo Conference, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - CBX Cleo Conference, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - CBX Cleo Conference, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - CBX Cleo Conference, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - CBX Cleo Conference, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - CBX Cleo Conference, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - CBX Cleo Conference, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - CBX Cleo Conference, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - CBX Cleo Conference, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - CBX Cleo Conference, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - CBX Cleo Conference, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - CBX Cleo Conference, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - CBX Cleo Conference, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - CESR III.5 Workshop Proceedings, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - LEPP, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - LEPP, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - LEPPHO Talks, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - LEPPHO Talks, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - LEPPHO Talks, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - LEPPHO Talks, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - LEPPHO Conference Papers, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - LEPPHO Conference Papers, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Physics Fest, June 1997 (Box 10)